{ "question" : "Tell me about ICD11 code 03 .", "answer": "This is a chapter about neoplasms of haematopoietic or lymphoid tissues.  Symptoms, signs or clinical findings of blood, blood-forming organs, or the immune system."}
{ "question" : "What is IDC11 code JB64.1 ?", "answer" : "Other diseases of the blood or blood-forming organs or certain disorders involving the immune mechanism complicating pregnancy, childbirth or the puerperium.  Any disease affecting pregnant females, characterised by pathological changes to the blood and blood-forming organs and pathological changes involving the immune mechanism that complicate pregnancy, childbirth, or the puerperium not classified elsewhere." }
{ "question" : "Tell me about JA42.0 .", "answer": "This is an ICD11 code for Intrapartum haemorrhage with coagulation defect.  A condition affecting pregnant females, excluding those caused by abruptio placentae and placenta praevia. This condition is characterised by excessive loss of blood with difficulties in blood clotting factors, after 20 weeks gestation until labour and delivery." }
{ "question" : "Tell me about ICD11 code 08 .", "answer": "This is a chapter about Diseases of the nervous system.  This is a group of conditions characterised as being in or associated with the nervous system."}
{ "question" : "What is ICD11 code 8A22?", "answer": "Lewy body disease.  Lewy body disease is a neurodegenerative disorder and the second most common form of dementia in the elderly after Alzheimer disease. Lewy bodies are histologically defined as intracytoplasmic eosinophilic neuronal inclusions in the cortex or brainstem." }
{ "question": "What does ICD11 8A20 mean?", "answer": "Alzheimer disease." }
{ "question" : "What is ICD11 code 20?", "answer": "This is a chapter about Developmental anomalies.  This chapter includes conditions caused by failure of a particular body site or body system to develop correctly during the antenatal period." }
{ "question" : "What is the meaning of ICD LD90?", "answer" : "Conditions with disorders of intellectual development as a relevant clinical feature." }
{ "question" : "Tell me about ICD11 code LD90.3.", "answer" : "Prader-Willi syndrome.  Prader-Willi syndrome is a rare genetic disorder characterized by hypothalamic-pituitary abnormalities with severe hypotonia during the neonatal period and first two years of life and the onset of hyperphagia with a risk of morbid obesity during infancy and adulthood, learning difficulties and behavioral problems or severe psychiatric problems. The disease affects 1/25,000 births. The severe hypotonia at birth, which leads to suckling and swallowing problems and delayed psychomotor development, partially improves with age. Characteristic facial features (a narrow forehead, almond-shaped eyes, a thin upper lip and down-turned mouth), as well as very small hands and feet, are frequently observed. After this initial phase, the most striking signs appear: hyperphagia and absence of satiety often leading to severe obesity in affected children as young as two years of age. The situation may deteriorate quickly without adequate outside controls and obesity is a major factor influencing morbidity and mortality in these patients. Other associated endocrine abnormalities contribute to the clinical picture of short stature due to a growth hormone (GH) deficiency and incomplete pubertal development. The degree of cognitive dysfunction varies widely from one child to another. It is associated with learning disabilities, and impaired speech and language development that are aggravated further by psychological and behavioral troubles. The disease is clinically and genetically heterogeneous. It is caused by anomalies involving the critical region of chromosome 15 (15q11-q13). The expert consensus is that diagnosis should be based on clinical criteria (Holm's criteria of 1993, revised in 2001) with confirmation by genetic analysis. Most cases are sporadic and familial recurrence is rare, information that should be provided by genetic counseling. Management should be global and multidisciplinary. Early diagnosis, early multidisciplinary care and GH treatment have greatly improved the quality of life of affected children. There are currently no long-term data on the effect of GH treatment in adults, particularly concerning its effect on the behavioral problems and degree of autonomy obtained. In adults, complications linked to obesity and the issue of autonomy continue to pose important problems." }
{ "question" : "What is LD2H.Y? ", "answer": "Other specified syndromic genetic deafness" }
